Guide to the Washington Office on Africa Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Regional and Country Files, 1970-1995; Series I
  - Countries
    - South Africa
      - South Africa Trade Unions, 1979-1992 (Box 45, Folder 497-499)
      - South Africa: United Nations, 1976-1978 (Box 75, Folder 797)
      - South Africa Violence, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 500)
      - South African Information Exchange Working Paper, 1987-1992 (Box 46, Folder 500a-519b)
      - Southern Africa DOSSIER, 1986-1990 (Box 47, Folder 520-522a)
    - Sudan - Zimbabwe
      - Sudan (and the Horn), 1990-1995 (Box 47, Folder 523-531)
      - Swaziland, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 532)
      - Tanzania, 1972-1995 (Box 48, Folder 533-535)
      - Togo, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 536)
      - Tunisia, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 537)
      - Uganda, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 538)
      - Western Sahara, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 539)
      - Zaire, 1990-1995 (Box 49, Folder 540-546)
      - Zaire, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 546)
      - Zaire, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 547)
      - Zaire Mailings, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 548)
      - Zaire Mailings, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 549)
      - Zambia, 1990-1996 (Box 50, Folder 550-551)
      - Zambia: Kenneth Kaunda to US, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 552)
      - Zimbabwe, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 553-555)
      - Zimbabwe, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 784-785)
      - Zimbabwe, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 556)
  - Worldwide
    - General, 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 557-560)
    - Economics, 1991, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 561-562)
    - Politics/Military, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 563)
    - Health, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 564)
    - Social Summit on Development, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 565)
    - United Nations, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 566)
- Issues, 1972-1995; Series II
  - Atrocities Pre-independence, 1976-1979 (Box 52, Folder 573)
  - Children in Africa, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 574)
  - Conflict Resolution, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 575)
  - Culture, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 576)
  - Debt, 1990-1994 (Box 52, Folder 577)
  - Education, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 578)
  - Environment, 1986-1992 (Box 76, Folder 813)
  - Environment, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 579)
  - Environmental Investigative Agency, 1989-1991 (Box 75, Folder 789)
  - Foreign Aid, 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 790)
  - Foreign Aid, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 791)
  - Foreign Aid, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 580)
  - Foreign Aid Reform, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 581)
  - Government and Politics: General, 1993-1995 (Box 53, Folder 582)
  - Government and Politics: General, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 583)
  - Government and Politics: Foreign Aid / Debt Relief, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 800)
  - Health, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 584)
  - Human Rights, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 585)
  - Human Rights, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 586)
  - Islamic "Extremists", 1995 (Box 53, Folder 587)
  - Legislative Research, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 806)
  - Liberation Movements, 1972-74 (Box 53, Folder 588)
  - Misc Documents and Publications, 1990-1994 (Box 53, Folder 589-592)
  - Misc Documents and Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 54, Folder 593-598)
  - Documents and Publications (American Muslim Council), 1994 (Box 54, Folder 599)
  - Misc Documents and Publications (Angola), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 600)
  - Misc Documents and Publications (Angola), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 601)
  - Misc Documents and Publications (Angola), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 602)
  - Misc Documents and Publications (Mozambique), 1991-1993 (Box 55, Folder 603)
  - Misc Documents and Publications (South Africa), 1993 (Box 55, Folder 604)
  - Organization of African Unity, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 819)
  - Organization of African Unity and the United Nations (Box 56, Folder 605)
  - Population, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 606)
  - Proliferation: General Reagan Non-proliferation policy, 1981-1984 (Box 56, Folder 607)
  - Proliferation: General -- Non-proliferation, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 607A)
  - Proliferation: General, 1977-1979 (Box 56, Folder 607B)
  - Proliferation: General, 1981-1984 (Box 56, Folder 607C)
  - Proliferation: IAEA Safeguards, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 608)
  - Proliferation: Congress: HAFAC Hearings 24 June 1982, 1981/84 (Box 56, Folder 609)
  - Proliferation:: Congress Senate Hearing 13 May, 1982, 1981/84 (Box 56, Folder 610)
  - Proliferation: Congressional Non-proliferation initiatives, 1981-1984 (Box 56, Folder 611)
  - Radical Right, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 612)
  - Rescissions, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 613)
  - Sports, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 614)
  - Stockpile-Government Stocks, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 615)
  - Structural Adjustment, 1990-1994 (Box 57, Folder 616)
  - Structural Adjustment, 1990-1994 (Box 57, Folder 617)
  - UN Peacekeeping Policy Review, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 796)
  - UN Policy on South Africa and US Response, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 798)
  - US Foreign Relations (General), 1992-1994 (Box 57, Folder 618)
  - US Foreign Relations (General), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 619-621)
  - US Foreign Relations ("International"), 1995 (Box 57, Folder 622)
  - US Foreign Relations (General), 1995 (Box 57, Folder 623)
  - US Foreign Relations (Africa), 1990-1995 (Box 57, Folder 624)
  - US Foreign Relations (Africa), 1990-1995 (Box 57, Folder 625)
  - US Foreign Relations (Africa), 1991 (Box 58, Folder 626)
  - US Foreign Relation (Africa), 1994 (Box 58, Folder 627)
  - US Foreign Relations (Angola), 1994 (Box 58, Folder 628)
  - US Foreign Relations (South Africa), 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 629)
  - US Foreign Relations (South Africa), 1990 (Box 58, Folder 630)
  - US Foreign Relations (South Africa), 1990-1994 (Box 58, Folder 631)
  - US Foreign Relations (United Nations), 1990-1994 (Box 58, Folder 632)
  - US Foreign Relations (Zaire), 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 633)
  - US State Department, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 803)
  - Uranium: Africa, Australia, France, Japan, 1977-1982 (Box 58, Folder 634)
  - Violence, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 635)
  - Women, Poverty and Role of US Aid, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 636)
  - World Bank, 1981-1995 (Box 59, Folder 637-639)
  - World Bank/IMF: World, 1992-1995 (Box 59, Folder 640-641)
  - World Bank /IMF, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 642)
- WOA Advocacy, 1972-1996; Series III
  - Advocacy Initiatives and Program Activity, 1988-1996 (Box 59, Folder 643)
  - Action Alerts/Press Releases, 1992-1994 (Box 59, Folder 644)
  - Action Alerts Program, 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 645)
  - Action Alerts, 1995 Jun (Box 60, Folder 646)
  - Action Alerts, 1995 Jun (Box 76, Folder 805)
  - Action Alerts, 1995 Jul - 1996 Feb (Box 60, Folder 647-652)
  - Action Alerts (March-April), 1996 Mar-Dec (Box 61, Folder 653-657)
  - Action Alerts (November-December), 1996 (Box 61, Folder 657)
  - Advocacy Network for Africa (ADNA), 1995 (Box 61, Folder 658)
  - Advocacy Network for Africa (ADNA), 1995 (Box 62, Folder 659-665)
  - Advocacy Network for Africa (ADNA), 1996 (Box 63, Folder 666-667)
  - AFL/CIO, 1990-1993 (Box 63, Folder 668)
  - AFL-CIO: African-American Labor Center, 1991-1995 (Box 63, Folder 669)
  - Africa Faith and Justice Network Archives, 1990-1993 (Box 63, Folder 670)
  - Africa Faith and Justice Network / NCC, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 671)
  - Africa Information Network (Dec-Jan), 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 672)
  - Africa Peace Committee, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 673)
  - Africa Peace Tour 1992 IOWA/New Hampshire (Box 63, Folder 674)
  - Africa Peace Tour, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 675)
  - African Studies Association, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 676)
  - African National Congress 80th Anniversary Celebration, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 677)
  - African National Congress 80th Anniversary Celebration, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 807)
  - AFSC Southern Tour, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 678)
  - AFSC Southern Tour, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 679)
  - American Committee on Africa, 1981-1985 (Box 75, Folder 799)
  - American Committee on Africa/Africa Fund, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 680-684)
  - American Foundation for Resistance International, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 684)
  - Arms Control and Foreign Policy Caucus 1993 (Box 65, Folder 685)
  - Association of Concerned Africa Scholars, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 686)
  - The Bush Legacy and Southern Africa: A post-Cold War Balance Sheet, Winter 1993 (Box 65, Folder 687)
  - Campaign to Preserve Global Leadership, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 688)
  - Center for Innovative Diplomacy (CID), 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 689)
  - Citizens Budget Campaign Workshop, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 690)
  - Coalition to Rethink US Aid to the Middle East, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 812)
  - Council on Inter-racial Books for Children, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 691)
  - Cross references Africa/Somalia, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 692)
  - DC Student Coalition Apartheid and Racism (DCSCAAR), 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 693)
  - Drought Mailings, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 694)
  - Education against Apartheid, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 695)
  - Educational Film Library Association, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 815)
  - Events Attended, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 814)
  - Events Attended, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 696)
  - Events Attended, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 801)
  - Events Attended, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 697)
  - The Film Fund, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 698)
  - Fifty Years Is Enough, 1992, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 699-701)
  - Global Perspective in Education, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 702)
  - Global Exchange, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 703)
  - Great Lakes Policy Forum, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 705)
  - Hill Mailings, 1992-1995 (Box 67, Folder 705)
  - Hill Mailings, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 816)
  - Institute For Contextual Theology News, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 706)
  - Interfaith (Achieves), 1992 (Box 68, Folder 707)
  - International Anti-Apartheid Movement (British), 1975-1979 (Box 68, Folder 708)
  - International Anti-Apartheid Movement (British), 1974-1994 (Box 68, Folder 709)
  - International Foundation for Electoral Systems, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 808)
  - International Mobilisation, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 710)
  - International Round Tabel on Nigeria (IRTON), 1996 (Box 69, Folder 723)
  - Key meetings, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 711)
  - Fr. Michael Lapsley, US visit of, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 712)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1992-1994 (Box 68, Folder 713)
  - Legislative Updates, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 714)
  - Lutheran Church: ELCA Strategy for Namibia, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 715)
  - Lutheran Church, 1974-1985 (Box 68, Folder 716)
  - Maryknoll Media Relations, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 717)
  - Media Reports, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 802)
  - Mozambique: Facts on, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 810)
  - Mozambique Program, Testimony, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 718)
  - Moose, Am. George: Meeting with, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 719)
  - Nambia: Facts on, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 810)
  - National Activist Briefing (Legislative Kit), 1990-1995 (Box 69, Folder 720)
  - National Black Child Development (NGO), 1994 (Box 69, Folder 721)
  - National Conference in Support of the African National Congress for New South Africa, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 722)
  - New Alliance Party Rainbow Lobby, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 724)
  - Parker Newsletter, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 725)
  - Republican Party, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 726)
  - Resources - Book and Film Lists, 1973-1980 (Box 69, Folder 727)
  - Resources - Book and Film Lists, 1973-1980 (Box 69, Folder 728)
  - Save the Africa Subcommittee II, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 728)
  - Sign On Letters, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 729)
  - Sign On Letters, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 730)
  - Somalia: How to Save Somalia, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 731)
  - South Africa: Aid and South Africa Briefing, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 732)
  - South Africa: Disinvestment from South Africa: 123 U.S. Companies Remain there, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 733)
  - South Africa: Letter: to Press, Bush from Senators 07/02/92: Re: Negotiations, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 734)
  - South Africa: Sanctions lifted, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 735)
  - South Africa: Research / Educational Centers / De Klerk Regime Implicated in Continuing Violence, 1981-1983, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 736)
  - South Africa: Vigil at South Africa embassy, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 737)
  - South Africa Working Group (SWAG), 1991-1993 (Box 70, Folder 738)
  - South Africa Working Group (SWAG), 1992 (Box 70, Folder 739)
  - South Africa Working Group (SWAG) (Jan-Mar), 1994 (Box 70, Folder 740)
  - South Africa Working Group (SWAG) (Jun-Jul), 1994 (Box 70, Folder 741)
  - South Africa Working Group (SWAG) (Aug-Dec), 1994 (Box 70, Folder 742)
  - South Africa: WOA Press Releases, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 786)
  - Southern African Research and Documentation Center (SARDC), 1990 (Box 70, Folder 743)
  - Southscan, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 744)
  - Speakers on Africa / South Africa, 1972-1982 (Box 70, Folder 745)
  - Clarence Thomas confirmation to Supreme Court, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 746)
  - UAM Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 71, Folder 747)
  - U.S. Foreign Policy: An Africa Agenda Conference Reports (APIC), 1993-1994 (Box 71, Folder 748)
  - Washington Inter-religious Staff Council (WISC): Statement of Principles and Procedures, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 749)
  - White House Conference on Africa, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 750)
  - White House Media Relations, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 817)
  - WOA Correspondence: Administration, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 751)
  - WOA Correspondence: Administration In/Out, Congress In, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 752)
  - WOA Correspondence: Congress In/Out, Administration Out, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 753)
  - WOA Legislative: 101st Congress: "article, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 752)
  - World Council of Churches, 1987-1991 (Box 76, Folder 818)
  - World Council of Churches Program Combat Racism: Hearing on, May 1988 (Box 71, Folder 753)
  - World Government of World Citzens, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 754)
  - Zaire A Nation Held Hostage, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 755)
  - Zimbabwe: Fact Cards Prepared for Zimbabwe Week, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 810)
- US Policy: Congressional and Administration, 1989-1995; Series IV
  - Bush Administration: Bush, Cohen, 1989-1990 (Box 72, Folder 756)
  - Clinton Administration: Christopher, Lake, Brynn, G. Moose, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 756)
  - Summers, Lawrence: Objections to nomination as Undersecretary for International Affairs at US Department of Treasury, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 757)
  - Hearing 02/06/92 Senate: Situation in Zaire and Somalia, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 758)
  - Hearing: 03/10/93 House: Recent Developments in Sudan, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 758)
  - Hearing: 11/06/91 Senate: Situation in Zaire, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 758)
  - Hearing: 10/26/93 House: Zaire: A Country in Crisis, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 758)
  - Hearing: 11/27/90 Senate: Situation in Sudan and Liberia, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 758)
  - Hearing: 02/23/90 House: U.S. Policy Toward Africa, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 759)
  - Hearing: 06/09/93 Senate: Liberia, Togo, and Zaire, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 759)
  - Hearing: 07/29/93 House: Current Events in Somalia, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 759)
  - Hearing: 09/30/93 House: U.S. Policy Toward Transition in South Africa, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 759)
  - Hearing: 03/14/91 House: Human Rights in Africa, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 760)
  - Hearing: 05/14/91; 06/26/91 Senate: Current Situation in the Horn of Africa, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 760)
  - Hearing: 06/23/92 House: Recent Events and US Policy in Kenya, Somalia, and Malawi, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 760)
  - Hearing: 03/31/93 House: Peace-keeping and Conflict Resolution in Africa, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 761)
  - USAID Report on the Performance of the Development Fund for Africa, 1988-1992 (Box 73, Folder 762)
  - Budget AID General, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 763)
  - Foreign Aid McConnell Bill Program, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 763)
  - House Subcommittee on Africa, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 763)
  - House Foreign Relations: Africa Subcommittee 103rd, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 763)
  - House Appropriations: Foreign Operations, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 763)
  - Senate Appropriations, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 763)
  - Boren, David Lyle (D-OK), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 764)
  - Bradley, Bill (D-NJ), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 764)
  - Bereuter, Doug (NE-1) Foreign Affairs Republican, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 764)
  - Burton, Dan (Indiana), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 764)
  - Dellums Ronald V Democrat. Cong Black Caucus, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 765)
  - Dornan, Robert K (California-38) Intelligence - Republican, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 765)
  - Dorgan Hyron (ND-1) Hunger Democrat, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 765)
  - Dymally, Mervyn M. (California-31) Black Caucus / Intl Affairs Democrat, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 765)
  - Flake Floyd H. (New York 6) Black Caucus Democrat, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 765)
  - Gejdenson, Sam ( Connecticut 2) Intl Affairs - Democrat, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - Gilman, Benjamin A. (New York 22) Intl Affairs Republican, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - Rep. Charles Hayes ( D-IL), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - McCurdy, Dave (Oklahoma 4) Intelligence - Democrat, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - Owens, Major R. (New York 12) Black Caucus - Democrat, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - Broomfield, Williams S, (Michigan 18) Intl Affairs Republican, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - Sawyer, Thomas C. (HI 14) Intl. Affairs, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 766)
  - Stokes, Louis (Ohio 21) Black Caucus - Democrat, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Towns, Edolphus (New York 1) Black Caucus _ Democrat, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Cranston, Alan (D-CA), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - D'Amato Alfons (R-NY), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - DeConcini, Dennis (D-AZ), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Hatch, Orrin G. (R-UT), 1991 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Hollings, Ernest F. (D-SC), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Inouye, Daniel K. (D-HI), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Kassebaum, Nancy Landon (R.KS), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Kennedy, Edward M. (D-MA), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Leahy, Patrick J. (D-VI) (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Mavroolesr, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Metzenbaum, Howard M. (D-OH), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Mitchell, George J. (D-ME), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Pell, Claiborne (D-RI), 1990 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - John Seymour, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Simon, Paul (D-IL), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Simpson, Alan K, (R-WY), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Wallop, Malcom (R-WY), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - With, Timothy E. (D-CO), 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep, Dave Obey (D-WI): Appropriations, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Sanford Bishop (D-GA) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Corinne, Brown (D-FL) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. William Cay (D.MO) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Eva Clayton (D-NC) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. James E. Clyburn (D-SC) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. John Conyers (D-MI) 10rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Ronald Dellums (D.CA) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Charles Diggs (Retired) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Cleo Fields (D-LA) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Maxine Waters (D-CA) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Mel Watt (D-NC) 103RD, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Rep. Albert Wynn (D-MD) 103RD, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 767)
  - Sen. Edward Kennedy (D-MA) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Gary Franks (R-CT) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Re[. Le Hamilton (D-IN) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Tony Hall (D-OH) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Alcee Hastings (D-FL) 103RD, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Earl Hilliard (AL) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Eddie Bernice Johnson (D-TX) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Harry Johnston (D-FL) Chair, House Africa Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Cynthia Mckinney (D-GA) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Carrie Meek (D-FL) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Kweisi Mfume (D-MD) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. John L. Mica (R-FL) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Eleanor Holmes Norton (DC0 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Donald Payne (D-NJ) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Me. Reynolds (D-EL) 103, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Bobby Scott (D-VA) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Josse Serrano (D-NY) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Gerry E. Studos (D-MA) 103rd, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Edolphus Towns (D-NY) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Rep. Walter Tucker (D-CA) 103rd, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 768)
  - Congressional Black Caucus - 1993, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 769)
  - Congressional Human Rights Caucus 1994 (Box 73, Folder 770)
  - Progressive Caucus 1993 (Box 73, Folder 770)
  - US Legislative; US AID, State Dept, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 771)
  - Legislation, Draft 09/06/91, Actions of the Government of South Africa, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 772)
  - Legislation 03/26/92 S. Res. 301: Ongoing Violence connected with Apartheid in South Africa, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 772)
  - Legislation: H. Con. Res. 270: Economic Sanctions on South Africa, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 772)
  - Legislation: Draft S. Con. Res.: Release of Nelson Mandela and Other Positive Developments, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 772)
  - Legislation H.R 2521 06/11/91 (Appropriation for Defence FY ending 09/30/92, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 772)
  - Legislation HR 5368 06/16/92 Appropriations/Foreign OP FY ending 09/30/93, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 772)
  - Legislation H.R. 1792 04/16/91 To Amend Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 773)
  - Legislation H.R. 4699 06/30/94 -- Antipersonnel Landmines, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 774)
  - Legislation: S. 956 04/25/91 To Amend Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 774)
  - The Penny Amendment, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 775)
  - H.R. 3458 South Africa Sanctions., 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - H. Con. Res. 270: No Modification of sanctions, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - H.R. 4590 (Dymally) (South Africa): Definition of Steel, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - S. Con. Res. 47 (Simon) South Africa Sanctions, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - S. Con. Res. 94/H. Con. Res. 282 (Simon/Wolpe) (S.A) Maintain Sanctions, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - H. Con. Res. 282 Release of Nelson Mandela and Other Positive Developments, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - H.J. Res. 480 (Hayes) (South Africa) "Nelson Mandela Week", 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - S.J. Res. 336 "South African Freedom Week", 1990 (Box 76, Folder 811)
  - H. Res. 48 South Africa): Meaningful Negotiations, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - H. Con Res. 67 (Owens) (South Africa) Conscientious Objector Asylum in U..S, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 776)
  - Pending Legislation Concerning sub-Saharan Africa, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 777)
  - Legislation: Draft 11/22/93 - Foreign AID Reform, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 778)
  - Legislation: S. 1856: Peace, Prosperity, and Democracy Act, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 779)
  - Legislation: S. 2216 06/07/94: Landmines Act, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 779)
  - Legislation: H.R. 21 01/03/89: Prohibit Investments in South Africa, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 788)
  - Legislation: S. 507 03/03/89: Prohibit Investments in South Africa, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 788)
  - Public Law 99-440 1986 (Box 74, Folder 783)
  - Public Law 100-203 1987 (Box 74, Folder 783)
  - Public Law 103-306. 23 1994 (Box 74, Folder 779)
  - Legislation: H. Con. Res. 131: Situation in Sudan, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 779)
  - Legislation H.R. 4238: Liberian Relief, Rehabilitation, Reconstruction, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 780)
  - Legislation: H.R. 3225: SA Transition Support Act of 1993 (Box 74, Folder 780)
  - Africa Conflict Resolution Act, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 781)
  - U.S. Response to the Drought in Southern Africa, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 782)